{
    "id": "ddbf1d55bd744b0485e71186436bc5c1",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If I were you, I …………………… be careful with the choice of my words.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "James is the …………………….. efficient of the two assistants we employed last month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "most",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother of the dead child was overwhelmed …………………. grief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I congratulate you …………………… .. your wonderful achievement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was so fastidious that she liked …………………… .. of the three designs I submitted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… .. a very long time, this city has been prosperous.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "For",
                "Since",
                "From"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You won’t have much difficulty …………………… making friends in Italy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Not many people are interested …………………… . algebra.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I was sorry when Alice moved to France. We ……………………. good friends since our school days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "have been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked …………………… . the edge of the valley.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "as far as",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}